Clay Coco

OBJECTIVE

Results oriented professional seeks a challenging and rewarding position that will utilize current and future skill sets in order to complement the organization's image and enhance efficacy of program objectives.

PROFILE

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT EXPERTISE

Extensive experience providing new business strategies and management services within the special event, program marketing, and community relations markets. In-depth understanding of core business structure, including process planning and modeling, provisioning and overall media management.

PROJECT MANAGEMENT AND BUSINESS ACUMEN

Successful record of leading teams in the development and completion of high-quality deliverables. Able to define, communicate, and fulfill the project's goals and break complex issues into manageable parts.

EXPERIENCE

NORTH LOUISIANA AREA HEALTH EDUCATION CENTER PUBLIC INFORMATION & MARKETING COORDINATOR

North Louisiana Area Health Education Center; Bossier City, LA

012-2014

Planned, organized, and directed overall communication strategies and public information activities for the organization. Managed, planned, directed, controlled and implemented a proactive communication program to enhance the reputation and visibility of the organization. Oversaw the organization's digital communication, including the content for the Web site and social media. Provided detailed reports of communications activities, including return-on-investment analyses. Supported communication goals of the organization. Participated in strategic planning with Program Directors and Coordinators. Identified communication needs and goals of the organization. Produced content for distribution through several information channels and platforms. Managed and handled several information channels and platforms.

MED JOB LOUISIANA HEALTHCARE RECRUITER

North Louisiana Area Health Education Center; Bossier City, LA Southwest Louisiana Area Health Education Center; Lafayette, LA

2012-2014 2008-2011

Coordinated communications with applicants and communities through the use of Practice Sights software. Conferred with hospitals, rural health clinics, federally qualified health centers, providers and communities to identify recruitment needs. Worked with healthcare facilities staff to develop a community profile. Developed recruitment strategies to attract qualified applicants and to fill specific job openings in the designated geographic region. Developed and maintains a network of contacts to help identify and source qualified candidates. Initiated contact with qualified candidates for specific job openings. Reviewed applications and interviews applicants to obtain work history, education, training, job skills, personal goals and objectives and salary requirements. Provided candidates information about positions, the State of Louisiana, communities and area facilities. Served as a liaison to the incentive programs offered by the State of Louisiana. Screened and referred candidates for interviews with communities; facilitates others in organization. Developed recruitment programs, marketing materials and other informational tools about the State of Louisiana and its opportunities. Assisted the Events Coordinator in the planning, implementation, and solicitation of exhibitors for Med Job Louisiana sponsored events. Coordinated and participated in job fairs and recruitment events. Developed and maintained contacts with medical schools, residency programs, other health professional training schools, alumni groups, and other public organizations to find and attract applicants. Made public presentations at universities, community meetings, organizations, association meetings, and job fairs regarding the services offered by Med Job Louisiana. Utilized internet online recruiting sources to identify and recruit candidates. Provided



information regarding facilities, communities, the State of Louisiana and job opportunities to potential applicants. Filed and maintained records on all candidates, placements, facilities, and communities for future reference. Assisted in the development and implementation of the annual marketing plan. Maintained records, prepared reports and correspondence relative to recruitment services and special projects including statistical information.

MED JOB LOUISIANA PROGRAM EVENTS & MARKETING COORDINATOR Southwest Louisiana Area Health Education Center; Lafayette, LA

2004-2008

Coordinated the marketing efforts of Med Job Louisiana to medical residency programs, schools of nursing, allied health and Louisiana medical employers through various mediums including, but not limited to, Web site updates, print and broadcast media, group presentations, and direct mail. Initiated and completed the planning, implementation and production of program events and materials. Developed and coordinated the submission of press releases, articles, email and direct mail pieces pertinent to program events and activities. Assisted program recruiters with efforts to establish and maintain relationships with hospitals representatives, residency programs, and schools of nursing and allied health. Instituted the design, development, and inventory of program marketing collaterals. Developed and distributed monthly program newsletter. Maintained data base of exhibitors and sponsors for program activities. Promoted the program recruitment services to statewide partners. Maximized contact opportunities between providers and employers during recruitment activities. Organized follow-up activities with residency programs and schools of nursing and allied health. Coordinated practice management workshops in collaboration with the Department of Health and Hospitals Bureau of Primary Care and Rural Health. Initiated and participated in program staff attendance at conferences or trade show events. Coordinated the scheduling and attendance at luncheons and educational forums for residency programs and schools of nursing and allied health. Cultivated and maintained relationships with hospital CEOs, executive staff of health care associations, sponsors and representatives of partner organizations. Cultivated and maintained working relationships with residency program directors, coordinators, residents and students through updates, event marketing, and program service marketing. Researched, developed and implemented the program events structure, and the evaluation of all components to determine any fundamental weaknesses or strengths. Partnered with LSUHSC-Shreveport to plan, coordinate and oversee the Educational Weekend while simultaneously maximized networking opportunities between employers and candidates on site. Researched and recommended potential program partnering opportunities. Maintained and updates MedJobLouisiana.com Web site events section as needed.

PREVENTION SPECIALIST

Southwest Louisiana Area Health Education Center; Lafayette, LA

2004-2004

Provided prevention education to at risk members of the community via facilitation of various programs tailored to meet the needs of the target population. Served as primary designer for all support materials concerning program promotion including brochures, flyers, and informational packets for presentations. Was responsible for media and community relations regarding project activities. Provided assistance in statewide healthcare recruiting and educational events.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF LOUISIANA AT LAFAYETTE Lafayette, LA — B.A., Public Relations, 2002

REFERRALS Available upon request.